Previously on desperate housewives
《绝望的主妇》  前情提要
Before we met, I was married to someone else but she died.
遇见你之前  我曾经结过婚  但是她过世了
Eddie's question begun
伊迪的疑心开始蔓延
What do you think if I and Katherine going to camp.
我和凯瑟琳一起去野营   你觉得如何
It would be fun.
一定很很有趣
And Dave's plan move forward
大卫的计划发展顺利
This is going to be fun.
一定乐趣无穷
Were you serious about going back to work.
你说要重新工作  是认真的吗
Lynette took a new path.
勒奈特人生旅程翻开崭新一页
Now is your turn.
现在轮到你了
Tell Carlos he's fired.
告诉卡洛斯  他被开除了
But is was Carlos' boss,
意外的是  卡洛斯的老板
He just kept telling me he loves her.
他一直不停的说  他有多爱他
Who was terminated
走到了生命尽头
I just wanted him to stop talking.
我只是想让他住嘴
Come on Gaby.
快点  加布
We'll be late.
我们要迟到了
Gabrielle Solis
加布丽尔·索利斯
Hated going to funerals,
厌恶一切葬礼
For all sorts of reasons.
原因众多
Black was not her color.
黑色不能衬托她的艳丽
Crying depressed her.
眼泪让她感到抑郁
And lilies made her sneeze.
而且她对百合花  过敏
Also Gabrielle despite any events
最重要的  凡是不以她为中心的场合
where she is not the center of attention.
她都厌恶出席
Luckily, at this funeral, that would not be a problem.
幸运的是  这一回  她正好是焦点人物
Gaby, i was hoping you'd be here.
加布  我一直希望你能来
Everyone is saying that you and carlos were there,
大家都说  你和卡洛斯在现场
You know, when maria killed bradley.
玛利亚杀死布拉德利的时候
You know, jody, i really don't think this is
茱蒂  这个时间和场合
The time or place to discuss gory details.
不应该谈这个话题吧
You're absolutely right.
你说的没错
Sit next to me at the wake.
守丧的时候坐在我旁边
I want to go home!
我想回家
Well, we just got here. the funeral hasn't even started.
我们刚到  葬礼都还没开始呢
Yeah, well, i have a feeling most of these vultures
对  在场的这些秃鹫
Didn't come to pay their respects to brad.
根本不是出于敬意
They're just here to pump us for dirt about his murder.
他们只是来打听小道消息的
Okay, even so, i can't be seen walking out of here early.
就算这样  我们也不能提早离场
These people are my coworkers.
这些都是我的同事
were your coworkers.Brad fired you
是你的旧同事  布拉德利开除你了
Remember?
没忘记吧
Yeah, and maria killed him eight hours later.
对  然后8个小时候  玛利亚杀了他
He might not have told anyone, so pipe down.
也许他还没告诉别人  冷静点
We don't need people thinking
不要让被人误会
That we put the knife in maria's hands.
是我们借玛利亚的手杀人
-Carlos.
-卡洛斯
oh, hi.
你好
Gaby, this is, uh, owen johnston, our c.e.o.
加布  这是约翰斯顿  我们的行政总裁
Oh, hi.
你好
How do you do? i know it's an awkward time,
你们还好吗  我知道现在时机不对
But i must catch a plane right after the service,
但葬礼之后我要赶飞机
-And i need to talk to you.
-我需要和你谈谈
about what?
谈什么
Bradley called me before he died.
布拉德利死之前给我打电话
He wanted to discuss your job performance.
说想讨论一下你的工作业绩
Well, what did he say?
那他怎么说的
Well, sadly,
可惜的是
By the time i returned the call, he was dead.
当我回电话时  他已经亡故了
Really?
是吗
But i think i know what he wanted to tell me.
但我应该没猜错他的用意
Based upon the big bonus he fought for carlos to have,
根据他以前努力为你争取的高额奖金
It's fairly obvious he was going to recommend a promotion.
很明显  他想升你的职
That was my guess, too.
我也这么猜想
The terrible irony is he didn't realize
讽刺的是  他没想到
The job he was recommending
你升职之后接管的
Would turn out to be his own.
将是他的职位
Wait.
等等
So you're offering me
你是要聘请我
Bradley's job as president of the company?
接替布拉德利  当公司总经理吗
I can't think of anyone better suited.
你是再合适不过的人选了
of course, it would be the same compensation package.
当然  薪水和他是一样的  保持不变
Please. tell me you'll accept.
恳请你  一定要答应
He sure will.
他当然会答应
The man has a plane to catch.
人家还要赶飞机呢
I'd be honored to step in for bradley.
我非常荣幸  能接替布拉德利
Good. i'm glad we've got that handled.
很好  很高兴我们把这事解决了
Now we can focus on the sorrow of this tragic day.
现在就能集中精神为他哀悼了
The same compensation package!
一样高的薪水
We're rich!
我们发财了
We are at a funeral.
现在是出席葬礼
Please be quiet.
安静点
Okay.
好
Yes, gabrielle solis hated going to funerals...
加布丽尔·索利斯憎恶葬礼
And for god sakes, stop smiling.
看在上帝的份上  别笑了
Mostly because she couldn't pretend to be sad
主要是因为  她无法在心情大好之时
When she wasn't.
假装悲伤9
You can find them on any sidewalk in any city...
在各地大街小巷走动的人们
People with agendas--
都有不为人知的目的
The woman who calls up an old friend
这女人拜访一位旧朋友
Because she wants to borrow some cash...
因为她需要点现金周转
The man who takes his boss to lunch
这个男子请上司吃午餐
Because he wants the corner office...
因为他觊觎一个更大的办公室
The girl who looks after her uncle
这个女孩照看自己的舅舅
Because she wants to be in the will...
因为她希望在遗产中分一杯羹
Yes, you can see these people almost everywhere.
确实  这样的人到处都是
Doing what they can to keep their agendas hidden.
将自己的用意深埋心底
Hello.
你好
I need to look someone up in your archives.
我需要查查你们档案上的一个人
It's a client, and he's, uh, a bit of a smooth talker.
是你们的顾客  他有点油嘴滑舌的
Just want to make sure that he's
我想确定一下
not giving me a run around."
别让他给骗了
Sure. what's his name?
没问题  他的名字是
David... dash.
大卫·达什
All i've got here are the obituaries.
我这里只有一些讣告
Anything else will take me a couple of days.
其他的资料需要一些时间
Fine. let's start with the obits.
好吧  我们就从讣告开始查
No david...
没有大卫
That's probably because he's not dead.
那是因为他还没死
Try lila.
试试查查里拉
Lila dash.
里拉·达什
Killed three years ago, car crash.
三年前身亡  死于车祸
That was his wife. give me that one.
那是他的妻子  给我看看
Okay.
好的
You want paige dash, too?
佩奇·达什的也要吗
Paige?
佩奇
Yeah, their daughter.
对  他们的女儿
"paige dash, 3 years old,
佩奇·达什  3岁
Daughter of lila and david."
大卫和里拉的女儿
It says here she died in the same crash.
上面说  她也在那场车祸中身亡了
Who are we dishing? i do hope it's not me.
这是在说谁的八卦呢  希望不是我
No, we've already covered you.
关于你  已经八卦完了
we've moved on to my daughter the thief.
现在正讨论我的小偷女儿
Oh, dear. what happened?
天啊  怎么了
I'm missing my small candy dish.
我的一个小糖果盘不见了
I had it last night when you guys were over for dinner,
昨晚你们过来吃饭时还在的
Because i remember orson admiring it.
当时奥森一直夸奖它  所以我印象深刻
Yes, i, uh... remember that.
没错  我  记得
Anyway, juanita went over before breakfast
胡安妮塔今天早上过去
To invite m.j. to her birthday party,
邀请MJ参加生日晚会
And, well, candy plus juanita.
胡安妮塔看到糖果
You don't have to be sherlock holmes
不用福尔摩斯也能破这个案件了
To crack this case. well, we don't know that for sure.
这也说不定的
I could have misplaced it.
也许我放错地方了呢
I'm sure it'll turn up somewhere.
说不定什么时候就出现了
Well... i'm off.
我还是先走了
Andrew, cancel my lunch.
安德鲁  取消我的午餐计划
No, everything's fine.
不  没什么事
Your stepfather's just misplaced a few things,
是你的继父  把几件小东西放错地方了
And i need to find them.
我得找找
Hey, tom. no, still waiting.
汤姆  没有  还在等呢
Big surprise. they're running behind at an ad agency.
大惊喜  他们的办公地方居然在一个广告部后面
So did any of those other places call back?
其他地方有没有回复呢
Seriously?
不会吧
Six interviews and nothin'?
6个面试  没人回复
Well, i should probably try and keep my game face on here.
这次我可要保持笑容了
I'll--i'll call you later. i love you. bye.
稍后再联系  我爱你  拜拜
Mariana!
玛莲娜
I had a feeling that you'd be interviewing for this!
我就猜到你会来这里参加面试
Hey, nikki.
你好  妮琪
So i guess anna should be showing up any minute, too.
我猜安娜应该很快也会来了吧
No. you didn't hear? she's pregnant.
不  你没听说吗  她怀孕了
Oh, my god. a kid and she just turned 30?
天啊  刚30就怀孕吗
Bye-bye, career. oh, don't start.
永别了  事业  别说这个话题
I'm gonna be 30 in 2 years. i feel so old.
再两年我就30了  感觉人都老了
Do you wanna know what's even sadder?
知道更惨的是什么吗
I just heard that veronica's looking for work,
我听说维罗妮卡在找工作
And she's 39.
她都已经39了
In this business?
在这行
After 35, they take you out back
35岁之后  他们就会带你到后门
and they shoot you in the face,
一枪毙了你
Lynette scavo.
勒奈特·斯加沃
We're ready for you.
轮到你了
Coming.
来了
Do me a favor.
帮帮忙
If you hear a gunshot, tell my four kids i love them.
如果你们听到枪声  转告我的4个孩子  我爱他们
Now as you listen to the music,
当你们听着音乐时
See what pops into your head.
展开你们的想象力
What shapes does it make you see?
这些音乐让你们想到什么形状
What colors are you thinking of?
什么颜色
Uh, why are the children drawing with crayons?
为什么孩子们拿着蜡笔在画画
They're supposed to be making clay vases.
他们应该做粘土花瓶的
Well, i wanted to do something more free.
我希望能课堂氛围更自由
It's an imagination-building exercise.
这是个训练想象力的练习
Looks like a lot of scribbling to me.
我看着就像乱涂乱画
Susan,
苏珊
These parents pay $22,000 a year to send their kids here.
孩子的父母每年支付2万2千美元
As art teachers, it's our job to give them
作为艺术教师  你应该教会他们
Something adorable to put on their desks
做些可爱的手工  摆放在桌子上
To smile at while they write those tuition checks.
好让父母们觉得  钱花得有价值
I mean,
我的意思是
No one's gonna find
没人会觉得
This meaningless chicken scratch adorable.
这些无意义的涂鸦  有何可爱之处
Not yours, mia. yours shows real promise.
不是说你  米亚  你画得很好
Jessie, you said that i could plan the lesson today,
杰西  你说我今天可以自行组织教学计划
And i think this is valuable.
我认为这很有意义
I'm just trying to be creative.
我只是想创新
Fine.
好吧
But you know where i stand.
但你应该知道我的立场
What's an "evalley-ation," miss susan?
苏珊老师  评估是什么意思
An evaluation?
评估嘛
Well, that is when someone judges your work
就是看你的表现
And gives you a grade on it.
给你打个分数
But don't worry. i'm not doing that today.
但是别担心  我今天不打分
No, they're doing it to you.
不  是他们要给你打分
Who?
谁
Miss jessie and principal hobson.
杰西老师和霍布森校长
I heard them talking.
我听到他们说了
Oh, right. that's not till later this year.
是的  不过要到年末
No, it's this week. i hope you don't get fired.
不  是这个星期  希望你不会被开除
The lady with the purple sweater
穿紫色毛衣的那个女老师
Argued with miss jessie like you did, and she's gone.
就像你一样  和杰西老师顶嘴  后来她走了
The lady with the purple sweater?
穿紫色毛衣的老师
I never learned her name. she wasn't here that long.
我不知道她名字  她没待多久
She was creative, too.
她也很有创意
All right, everyone.
好了  大家
Grab some clay. we're making vases.
拿些粘土  我们要开始做花瓶了
Darling, i'm home.
亲爱的  我回来了
Oh, and i'm famished!
饿得快晕倒了
What are we having for dinner?
晚餐吃什么
How about a confession?
忏悔大餐如何
Sit down.
坐下
Start talking.
坦白从宽
What do you want me to say?
你想让我说些什么
I want you to explain to me
我想让你解释
Why this insanity is still going on.
为什么还干这些疯狂的事
When you stole that tape recorder,
你偷了那个录音笔
You said it was a onetime thing,
你说是最后一次
An impulsive act of revenge.
是报复的冲动
It was, at first.
刚开始是这样子的
But then...
可是后来
I know it sounds odd, but...
我知道听起来很怪
It started giving me a thrill.
这让我觉得很兴奋
A thrill?
兴奋
Stealing a ceramic duck gives you a thrill?
偷了一个陶瓷鸭子让你兴奋
It's hard to explain.
这很难解释
Well, maybe you'd feel more comfortable
好吧  也许跟专业人士谈谈
Talking to a professional.
会感觉更不错
A psychiatrist?
看心理医生
Good heavens. bree, i'm not crazy.
天哪  布里  我没病
Look, i'll stop.
听着  我以后不这样了
I'll--i'll tell everyone i'm sorry
我  我会跟所有的人道歉
And return everything.
归还所有的东西
You will do no such thing. from this moment on,
不许再做这种事情了  从现在开始
you're forbidden of entering any of our friends’ home
不许去朋友们家
how we get this things back
那怎么把这些还回去
i'll take care of it
不用你操心
I'm so glad you could make it.
很高兴你能来
I know i sprung this on you at the last minute
你能赶来  我太激动了
I was just gonna watch a dvd and order some takeout,
我打算看看影碟  再叫点外卖
So i'm looking forward to a home-cooked meal.
我很期待家常菜
Oh, well, keep looking,
好吧  只能期待了
'cause i don't cook, and shanghai panda delivers.
我不会做饭  叫了海熊猫外卖
Oh. well, that'll be fine.
好的  挺好的
You know, susan,
苏珊  你知道吗
I was a little surprised to get your invitation.
收到你的邀请我挺惊讶的
Oh, well, you know,
你知道
I just think that school is such a formal environment,
我只是想学校是个正式的场合
And i thought it would be nice if we could let loose
我认为如果我们能放松一点  喝点酒
And drink a little wine, get to know each other.
相互加深一下了解
Oh, my gosh.
天哪
-What?
-怎么了
look at you.
看你
You're like that schoolmarm in the movies
你看起来像电影里披着头发的
Who lets down her hair and va-va-va-voom.
女教师  真漂亮
I've never gotten a va-va-va-voom before.
我从来没听过这样的赞美
Thanks. you look nice, too.
谢谢  你看起来也很不错
Oh, please. i didn't even get a chance to change.
拜托  我都没什么机会改变
My ex was late picking up m.j.,
我的前夫该来接MJ了  他迟到了
Which is insane, 'cause he lives right across the street.
他神经了  因为他就住在马路对面
Your ex lives across the street?
你的前夫就住在对面
He decided to shack up with my best friend.
他决定跟我的好朋友同居
And people wonder why i'm through with men.
居然还有人奇怪  我为什么受够男人了
So what are we toasting to?
我们庆祝什么
Getting to know each other better.
为了更深一步的了解
Oh, napkins.
忘了餐巾
I'll drink to that.
这非常值得干杯
Oh, hey, mike. come on in.
你好  麦克  快进来
I went a little crazy at the camping supply store.
我在露营商店买的有点多了
Hey, check this out. i got katherine her own lantern.
看看这个  我给凯瑟琳准备了提灯
I know she was a little worried
我知道她有点担心
About finding the latrine in the middle of the night.
半夜起来找厕所
Uh, actually, that's, uh, why i came by.
事实上  我  我就是为这事来的
Katherine sort of bailed.
凯瑟琳要放鸽子了
Bailed? you mean she's not going camping with us?
放鸽子  你意思是他不跟我们去露营了
Ah, she's really sorry,
她很抱歉
But she's gotta get her taxes done.
但是她必须把税交了
So katherine is blowing us off for taxes.
所以凯瑟琳因为交税不能去了
Also, i think she's worried she'd just be a third wheel.
另外  我想她是担心她会拖我们后腿
What? oh, come on.
什么  得了吧
I mean, this trip is as much about her as it is about us.
我是说  她对我们来说也很重要啊
Tell her she's gotta come.
告诉她一定得来
First of all, i don't tell katherine to do anything.
首先  我不会命令凯瑟琳做任何事情
And it'll be better with just us guys.
而且我们来一趟男人之旅也不错
We can burp and scratch to our heart's content.
我们可以随心所欲的打嗝  搔痒
Besides, katherine was never
另外  凯瑟琳本来
Part of the original plan anyway.
也不在我们的计划中
No, she wasn't.
是啊  是没她
All right, i'll, uh, see you saturday.
好吧  我会  周六见
Yeah.
好的
You're not listening to me.
你没在听我说
I'm not saying i'm giving up on love.
我不是说我打算放弃爱情
I'm saying i've already given up.
我的意思是我已经放弃了
No. i-i will not let you.
不行  我不会让你放弃的
You are too smart and funny and adorable.
你这么聪明  幽默  可爱
Am i?
是吗
It's been a long time since i've been complimenit like that
已经很久没有人这样恭维过我了
Well, i mean it.
我是认真的
Anyone would be lucky to have you.
能跟你在一起的人  是他的福气
You are a catch.
你很有魅力
Jeez. how did it get so late?
天哪  怎么已经那么晚了
Is there a school policy on showing up to work drunk?
学校明令禁止酒后上班吗
It's frowned upon.
当然不行
I've had the best time tonight.
我今晚过得很愉快
Oh, me, too.
我也是
You know, i think we should probably keep this between us.
你知道  今晚的事情是我们的秘密
We don't want people talking at work.
我不想同事们说三道四的
it'll be our secret?
我们的小秘密
So... you think you might wanna do this again sometime?
那么  你什么时候还想再聚一次吗
It's a date.
你在约我
Va-va-va-voom!
太棒了
S-so what kind of kiss are we talking about?
这么说你们接吻了  哪种类型的
A regular kiss on the mouth...
就是嘴对嘴接吻啊
That lasted a little longer than i thought it would.
比我想象的时间长了一点
So was it a good, old-fashioned american kiss
是美国的老式接吻
Or are we talking the infinitely superior french variety?
还是法式多样的激情吻
Okay, i'm probably just blowing this out of proportion.
好吧  我刚才没说清楚
I mean, she never even said anything about being gay.
她从来没说提过一句同性恋
Well, that doesn't make any difference. right, lee?
好吧  说不说出来都一样  是吧  李
Why ask me?
为啥问我啊
Aside from the occasional parade,
除了偶尔的游行外
Gay men rarely interact with lesbians in the wild.
男同志跟女同志没什么关系
Susan, if you're not sure what she meant by it,
苏珊  如果你不确定她那是什么意思
Why don't you just have a talk with her?
为什么不直接跟她谈谈
Oh, that would be way too awkward. she's my boss.
那样太尴尬了  她是我上司
She's your boss?
她是你的上司
Let her kiss you again, then sue her.
那就让她再亲你一次  然后控告她
Okay, we're gonna figure this out for you.
好了  我们会帮你弄明白的
Were her eyes open or shut?
她眼睛是睁着的还是闭着的
I don't know.
我不知道
Well, how many seconds did the kiss last?
好吧  你们亲了多长时间
I don't remember.
我不记得了
Oh, for god sakes.
看在上帝的份上
Was it this... mm.
是这样吗
Or was it this...
还是这样
The second one?
第二种
Congratulations. you're now dating a lesbian.
恭喜你  你在跟同性恋约会
See you at the parade.
一起去游行吧
Hey, gaby?
你好  加布
I'll see ya.
再见
I wanted to ask you something. feel free to say no.
有个小小的请求  你可以拒绝
Oh, honey, i'm flattered, but i
亲爱的  你过奖了  可是我
only did that to hope this is no
刚才那么做只是帮苏珊
Yeah, this isn't about that.
不是那件事
Um, i wanted to say i heard about carlos' big promotion.
我想说的是  卡洛斯升职的事儿
Congratulations.
恭喜你
Thank you. i mean, it's said how it happened,
谢谢  我是说  这一切怎么发生的啊
But, you know, when opportunity knocks,
可是  你知道的  机会找上门来
You gotta answer the door, right?
-你就得抓住  对吧
absolutely.
没错
Now you know i'm looking for work?
你看  我现在正在找工作
-Oh, yeah. how's that going?
-是啊  怎么样了
not great.
不太顺利
See, while i was working at scavo's,
我在斯加沃之家工作的时候
I got seven years older, which is weird,
老了七岁  真奇怪
Seeing as how all the c.e.o.s got seven years younger.
看起来那些CEO们怎么更年轻了
The bottom line is, no one wants to hire someone
底线是  没人想雇佣那些
Who could have made out with their dad on prom night.
和自己老爸同岁的职员
Anyway, i hear carlos
总之  我听说卡洛斯
Is looking for a new director of marketing.
在找新的市场经理
Think you could put in a good word for me?
你看能不能帮我美言几句
I don't know.
我不清楚
Y-you don't know?
你不清楚
Well, i thought you did advertising.
好吧  我以为你是做广告的
Yes, i helped advertise what companies decided to market.
是啊  我做广告  公司依据广告决定市场
It's the same thing.
是一回事
Come on. you know i'd be great.
好了  你知道我很棒的
I guess.
我想是吧
You guess? gaby...
你想  加布
Look, lynette, you're my friend, and i love you,
听着  勒奈特  我们是朋友  我爱你
But as far as knowing if you're any good at your job...
可是就我所知你在工作上的成绩...
Enough with the shrugging.
别耸肩了
- Come on.
-别这样
you're putting me in a tough spot.
你让我很为难
Carlos is under a lot of pressure now,
卡洛斯现在压力很大
And he's not really in a position
再说他没站稳脚跟
- To be taking big risks.
-冒不能这么大的风险
you think i'm a big risk?
你觉得我是个大风险
Okay, that's it.
好吧  就这样吧
Fourth shrug. i'm out.
耸了四次肩  我不求你了
Thanks for your help.
多谢你的帮助
Yeah, just follow the road as it curves.
是的  沿着路往前走
We're the second house on the left. okay, bye.
我们是左边的第二个房子  好的  再见
Oh, place looks great, babe. thanks for doing this.
宝贝儿  布置的很漂亮  太谢谢你了
It's all part of being the president's wife.
这是经理夫人应该做的
So tell me about your new hire.
跟我说说你新雇的人吧
she's gonna be you no.2.
她会接你的班吗
Yeah, and i'm lucky to get her.
对啊  很庆幸能雇到她
Smart as a whip, harvard m.b.a.
相当聪明  哈佛大学的MBA
I've probably mentioned her before.
我可能提起过她
Lucy blackburn?
露西·布莱克本
Maybe i'll go put on some music.
再来点音乐
Lucy blackburn?
露西·布莱克本
Please tell me it's a coincidence that
告诉我这是个巧合
Your new v.p. has the same name as your ex-girlfriend.
新副经理跟你的前女友名字一样
She wasn't my girlfriend.
她不是我女朋友
We were roommates. we shared an apartment.
我们以前是室友  一起租的公寓
You told me you slept with her.
你告诉过我  你跟她上过床
well, it was a small apart
好吧  那公寓很小
Come on. it was a casual thing,
别这样  那是个意外
and it was a million years ago.
都过去那么长时间了
I don't care! why couldn't you have told me this
我不管  她要来咱们家之前
Before she's about to appear on my doorstep?
你怎么没告诉我
I wanted to... but you were always next to something sharp.
我打算说的  可是你身边总有利器
Gaby, i am in over my head with this new job,
加布  这份新工作让我晕头转向
And i need lucy's help. please don't be jealous.
我需要露西的帮助  别嫉妒好吗
I'm not jealous. it's just... you can't hire her.
我不是嫉妒  就是有点  你不能雇她
I'm mrs. president, and i get a vote.
我是总裁夫人  我有权投票
There she is. now please, i'm begging you...
她来了  求你了  我求求你
Well, you can beg all you want.
好吧  随你怎么求
I am not on board with this!
我不会同意的
Hey, lucy!
你好  露西
Hey!
你好
Hi. i'm lucy. you must be gabrielle.
我是露西  你一定是加布里尔
You can call me gaby.
叫我加布好了
Come on in!
快进来
I'm on board.
我同意了
I got a bead on charlie fields for c.f.o.
我盯上了查理的首席财务长官
Charlie fields? there's no way you're gonna get him.
查理那边  他不可能同意的
He's the number two guy at brewster & parent.
他是布鲁斯特家族公司的二把手
Relax. it'll take some maneuvering,
别紧张   需要耍点手段
But i'll make it happen.
-一定能成
how?
要怎么办
Carlos, you're the president.
卡洛斯  你是经理
It's best you don't know where the bodies are buried.
这种细节你最好不要知道
Well, speak of the devil.
说曹操曹操到
If you'll excuse me,
我去接个电话
I have some professional ethics that need compromising.
我有点工作上的事要解决
Wow. now i know why you wanted to hire her.
现在我知道你为什么要雇她了
She's a force of nature. mm,
她天生谈判好手啊
you should see her close of a deal.
你该看看她和别人谈条件的
I'll bet. ahh. so were you surprised when the door opened?
肯定厉害  开门的时候你很惊讶吗
- What do you mean?
-什么意思
well, she's
显然
obviously stopped counting calories.
自从和你告别后
Since the last time you saw her.
她就再没上过磅秤了吧
No, she looks about the same.
没啊  她和以前一样
What? but...
什么  但
You two used to have sex.
你们上过床啊
Yeah. so?
是啊  怎样
So don't get me wrong-- she's attractive.
没别的意思  她确实很迷人
It's just... she's not really your type.
只是  不是你喜欢的那种
Your type is skinny model.
你喜欢的是苗条模特
Okay, so you're not gonna see her on the round way
没错  你估计是看不到她走T台了
- Except maybe at an airport.
- 在机场就不一定
gaby!
加布
You think i'm that shallow, that all i go by is looks?
我有那么肤浅吗   只看外表吗
Yeah, i thought that was something we had in common.
对啊  这不是我们的共同点吗
Look, lucy is brilliant and witty
露西智慧过人
And has more confidence than anybody i've ever met.
是我认识的人中最自信的
That type of personality can be very seductive.
这种品质非常有魅力
- Someone light me a cigar.
- 给我点烟庆功吧
you got him?
你拿下他了
I find poaching is easier when you lead with,
我发现当你说"工资翻倍"的时候
"we'll double your salary."
挖人会更简单
Sizzle me.
戳下我
Ah, there it is,
就是这样
That thrill you get from taking something that's not yours.
这种把别人的东西据为己的快感
Hey, are you still looking for a marketing director?
你还在招聘营销总监吗
I have a friend
我有个朋友
That i would love to see working with you two.
要能和你们一起工作就太好了
No problem, bree.
没问题  布里
We buy aspirin by the pound in this house.
我们家的阿司匹林用磅来算的
I'll get you some.
给你一些吧
Ah, you're a lifesaver!
你真是救世主啊
Yes, we have lots of screwdrivers.
我家有好多螺丝刀
What kind do you need? phillips head?
要哪种  梅花起子么
Yes, that would be lovely.
对  太好了
I don't have cumin, but i probably have cinnamon.
没有小茴香子  但应该有肉桂
Oh. close enough.
差不多啦
Yeah, no problem. two eggs coming right up.
好的  两个鸡蛋嘛
Oh! wait.
等等
I made omelets this morning, so i'm all out.
早上我做了煎蛋卷  鸡蛋用完了
Oh, that's all right. i'll just go to the store.
没事  我去商店好了
Where did that come from?
那个是哪来的
Oh. i don't know, but it's awfully cute.
我不知道  不过真可爱
Unbelievable.
难以置信
Juanita, get your butt down here.
胡安妮塔  给我滚下来
Why are you, uh, calling juanita?
你叫胡安妮塔干吗
To find out what mccluskey's sleeping mexican
问她为什么麦克卢斯基的墨西哥睡娃
Is doing in my house.
会在我家
- That's not yours?
- 那不是你的
no. why would you think that?
不是啊  为什么
Oh! uh, i don't know. but, you know, there it is.
不知道  但它就在这啊
It's been sitting on mccluskey's porch for years.
它在麦克卢斯基家走廊里很多年了
I keep telling her how racist it is.
我一直跟她说这个有多种族歧视
First the candy bowl and now this?
先是糖果碗  又是这个
How many times have i told you not
我告诉你多少次
- to steal?
- 不要偷东西
i didn't take that,
我没拿那个
Juanita, you play with it every
胡安妮塔  我们每次到麦克卢斯基家
time we go by Ms. Mccluskey,
你都要玩这个
Now either tell me the truth,
要么说实话
Or i'm gonna cancel your birthday party.
要么我就取消你的生日派对
- I am telling you the truth!
- 我说的是实话啊
that's it. party's over!
够了  别想要派对了
Gaby! aren't you being a little harsh?
加布  你是不是太严厉了
I mean, perhaps she didn't take it.
可能不是她拿的呢
Well, then how else did it get here?
那它还能怎么来的
Maybe she did it.
也许是她拿的
Juanita!
胡安妮塔
Whenever my children stole,
若是我的孩子偷东西
I sent them to bed without any supper.
他们就得饿着肚子睡觉
Just a thought.
随便说说
Orson?
奥森
Orson!
Orson! orson!
奥森  奥森
Orson!
奥森
No!
别这样
- Hi, bree!
- 布里  是你啊
what were you doing at bob and lee's?
你在鲍勃和李家干吗
Well, they invited me over for coffee.
他们叫我喝咖啡啊
After I told you to stay out of the neighbors' houses?
我说过不准到邻居家去的吧
You stole again, didn't you?
你又偷东西了  对吧
No. no, i didn't.
没啊  我没偷
What are you hiding behind your back?
你背后藏了什么
Nothing.
没什么
It's mine.
这是我的
You're telling me
你是说
You own a mug with a picture of
你有个大杯子  上面画着
bernadette peteman in Gypsies
吉普赛窃贼吗
This is quite a resume you got here.
你的条件看起来不错啊
Northwestern, huh?
西北大学
Yep. thank you.
对  谢谢
So, lynette
那么  勒奈特
How old are you?
你多少岁
Mr. vivinetto,
威纳特先生
- I'm not obligated to answer. it's the law.
- 我可以不回答  法律没这规定
right, right.
对  对
I was only asking 'cause i-i also went to northwestern,
只是问问  我也是西北大学的
And i thought maybe we crossed paths there. oh.
也许在哪见过呢
What--what year did you graduate?
你哪年毕业的
Well, if i was dumb enough to answer that,
要是我真傻到会回答你
I never would've gotten into northwestern.
就进不了西北大学了
I-i understand, but, uh, i'm gonna be honest here.
这我理解  老实说
We have certain accounts that
我们公司对职员
cater to a speci with the-- i'm
有某些硬性规定
Okay, i'm gonna stop you. what is this obsession with age?
到此打住吧  为什么执着于年龄呢
I am a vital woman with passion
我是一个活力十足的女人
And a library of knowledge when it comes to this industry.
在广告业算是学富五车
Why doesn't that count for something?
-这些能力都比不上年龄吗
what i'm saying is,
我是想说
We just landed the cosgrove's revitalizing serum account.
我们刚研发了斯格罗夫活肤滋润霜
It's an antiwrinkle cream, and i need someone more mature
有抗皱功能  我需要一名成熟女性
Who can identify with the--
-她的年龄应该达到
i'm 54.
我54岁了
He didn't even flinch.
他眉头不皱一下
I said i was 54, and he bought it.
我说我54岁  他居然信了
There was not a "wow, you look great for your age!"
居然没有夸奖我保养得当
Not even a courtesy gasp.
起码假装惊讶一下嘛
Look, you got the job. you're making $80,000 a year.
管他呢  你得到工作了  年薪8万呢
What--what does it matter?
这种小事算什么
It matters because i'm only 43, and i look like i'm 39.
有关系  因为我只有43岁  看起来应该像39岁
You're 43? but i'm-- i'm 2 years younger than you,
你43岁吗  我比你小两岁
And i--
-我已经
nobody cares how old you are, tom.
谁管你多少岁了  汤姆
-Great news! you got the job!
-好消息  你应聘上了
how'd you hear about it?
从哪里听说的
Hear about it? honey, i did it.
听说  宝贝  是我促成了
i talked to carnow what to say
我和卡洛斯谈过了  他答应了
That job.
那个工作啊
Um... i don't know what to say.
我不知道该说什么好
Say, "how do i thank you, greatest friend in the world?
说  该如何感谢你  你真是世界上最伟大的朋友
What's your birthstone?"
-你的诞生石是什么
well, thank you, greatest friend,
谢谢  伟大的朋友  但
But i just accepted another job.
我刚接受了另一份工作
Well, un-accept it. you have to take this job.
那再拒绝它  你必须接受我的提供
It's essential that you be there.
-你的作用至关重要
why?
为什么
Because it's a great opportunity.
因为这是千载难逢的良机
I'm confused. before, you didn't even want to talk to him.
我迷惑了  刚开始你还不愿意和他谈
You weren't even sure i was good.
还质疑我的能力
Yeah. yes, and then i went home and thought,
对  对  后来我回到家仔细想
What a horrible thing to say to such a dear, dear friend
对那么亲密的朋友说这话  多伤人啊
Who's probably really, really good at her job.
这个朋友也许还特别有能力
So...
所以
I said, "carlos, you have to hire lynette."
我就说  卡洛斯  你必须雇佣勒奈特
I... don't know.
我  不确定
Well, he'd have to match my current offer.
薪水必须和我现在的一样
Yeah, okay. what are they paying?
好  现在的年薪多少
$100,000 a year.
年薪10万元
I don't think that'll be a problem.
这不成问题
By the way, you're gonna be reporting to this woman lucy.
顺便提提  你要向这个叫露西的女人报到
She's a real star,
她能力超强
So you're gonna wanna keep an eye on her.
你得好好盯着她
Decaf soy latte-- your favorite.
低咖啡因大豆拿铁咖啡  你的最爱
Thanks.
谢谢
I was thinking about the other night...
-我正在想那天晚上
mm, me, too.
我也是
Maybe friday you could come over to my place,
也许星期五  你应该到我家来
And we could hang out or...
我们可以一起放松放松
You know, i-i think you may have
我觉得  也许你
gotten the wrong impressiong
对我有点误解
I'm not...
我并不
Into women.
喜欢女人
Nice boots.
靴子不错啊
I thought it was gonna rain.
我以为会下雨呢
I'm not gay.
我不是同性恋
Mm-hmm, then what was all that stuff about the other night?
那那天晚上算怎么回事
The--the touching my knee? the "oh, you look so sexy"?
抚摸我的膝盖  夸赞我性感
The good night kiss?
还有晚安吻
Oh, well, that kiss was all you.
那都是你主动的
Oh, it was?
是吗
I seem to remember you being there and not pulling away.
我似乎记得你站着  没推开我
Well, that's because--
那是因为
Why didn't you say something then?
-当时怎么不说呢
because i--
因为我
Because you're tired of living a lie.
-因为你厌恶谎言了
what?
什么
I was you 20 years ago, susan.
苏珊  你就像20年前的我
You're obviously worried
你明显在担忧
There's a lesbian inside of you trying to get out.
体内的同性恋因子会爆发
Actually, i'm more worried about the lesbian
其实  我更担心的是外面的同性恋因子
That's outside of me trying to get in.
想进入我的身体
Um, can we just teach the class and talk about this later?
我们先上课  稍后再谈行吗
Fine.
行
Shouldn't you be doing your taxes?
你不是应该去交税吗
Oh! god, dave! you scared me.
大卫  你吓到我了
Oh, sorry about that. oh.
我表示歉意
What's this i hear about you not going camping?
怎么我听说  你不想去露营了
Oh, well, it is that time of year,
每年的这个时候
And i got all these receipts to go through.
我总是有很多菜谱要看
I gotta say, i'm mighty disappointed.
我必须说  我非常失望
Please. i'm sure you're relieved
拜托  应该是松一口气吧
There won't be a girl tagging along
不会有女孩子拖后腿
To spoil all your macho fun.
毁掉你们的男人之夜
Well, see, now that's where you're wrong.
你这么想就错了
I mostly saw this trip
我把这次露营
As a chance to get to know you better.
-当成是了解你的机会
me? why?
为什么
Katherine, the truth is, i don't have a lot of friends.
凯瑟琳  事实上我朋友不多
Maybe that's why mike's become so important to me.
所以麦克对我来说很重要
And ever since you came into his life,
自从你走进他的生活
Well, i can see the change.
我看到了他的变化
He's so much happier, so much more relaxed.
他更加的开心  更加的放松
You've given him this sort of inner peace.
你给了他内心的平静
I just thought it would be cool
我觉着这样不错
To become buddies with the woman who did that for my friend.
和好友的挚爱成为朋友
Well, when you put it that way...
既然你都这么说了
So you'll go camping with us?
你会一起来露营吗
I'll go start packing my fleece.
我现在就开始收拾
Fantastic.
棒极了
Dave?
大卫
Do you really think
你真的觉得
I've made that much of a difference in mike's life?
我对麦克有那么重要吗
Oh, absolutely.
绝对的
If he ever lost you...
如果他失去你
It would destroy him.
生活就算毁了
Okay, class, let's see how
同学们  我们来看看
Our animals of africa drawings are going.
非洲之旅的动物素描画的如何
Oh, emma, this is beautiful.
艾玛  画非常的美
Emma drew a gazelle. isn't she pretty?
艾玛画了一个瞪羚羊  是不是很漂亮呢
Zachary, is that a rhinoceros?
扎克里  你画的是犀牛吗
Wow! he looks so big and strong.
它又大又壮
I love rhinos.
我喜欢犀牛
Do you, susan? do you really?
你确定吗  苏珊  真的喜欢吗
Excuse me?
你说什么
I'm just saying, if you were on safari
我是说  当你狩猎远行时
And you saw a sleek gazelle
看到一头可爱的瞪羚羊
Next to a grunting, sweaty rhino...
边上站着一头臭汗一身的犀牛
Your eye wouldn't go straight to the gazelle?
难道你不会直奔羚羊吗
Though i would definitely appreciate the...
尽管我欣赏
Beauty of the gazelle,
瞪羚羊的小巧美
Uh, if i was going to take a trip to africa...
但倘若我去非洲远足
I would be more excited to see the rhinos.
看到犀牛我会更加激动些
I like rhinos, too.
我也喜欢犀牛
Yes, we know, jeffrey.
是的  我们知道了  杰夫瑞
We've all seen you playing hopscotch at recess.
我们都见着你躲在角落玩"跳房子"  (暗指女孩子气)
Are you gonna tell me
别告诉我
That you've never had any experience with gazelles?
你从没有和瞪羚羊相处的经历吗
Not even in college?
在大学里也没有吗
No.
没有
And... i was on the softball team.
此外  当时我是垒球队的
Look, susan, why don't you just say it?
苏珊  为何不直话直说
This particular gazelle
这一只瞪羚羊
Isn't young enough for you,
太老了配不上你
And you don't want to hurt my feelings.
你不明说  只是不想伤我的心
That is not true, and i think we are dangerously close
事实并非如此  我觉得我们的暗喻
To no longer speaking in metaphor.
接近说破的边缘了
Well, then why were you so interested in me
那一开始  你为什么对我
In the first place?
这么感兴趣
Why did you ask me to your house?
干嘛要邀请我去你家
Because i wanted you to give me a good evaluation.
因为我希望你能给我一个好的评价
I see.
我明白了
It was nice knowing you, miss susan.
认识你很高兴  苏珊老师
The problem--how to attract high net worth clients
问题来了  如何在经济萧条时期
In a down economy.
来吸引高端客户
The solution? be creative.
解决方案必须带有创意
Christie's is hosting its first ever "sea auction"
克里斯蒂拍卖行正准备在圣巴斯的游艇上
On a yacht in st. barths.
举办第一个航海拍卖会
I see a boat full of millionaires
想象一艘游艇上满载着
Waiting to be wooed.
等待追崇者的富翁
This is not a bad idea.
这个主意不错
Besides, i haven't been to st. barths
而且  自从你为我的第一次升职
Since you took me there to celebrate my first promotion.
在那儿举办庆功会至今  我还没去过圣巴斯
That was a fun weekend.
那个周末真有意思
Yeah.
是的
-Let's do it.
-那就这么办吧
yep.
好的
-I gotta take this. i'll be right back.
-我接个电话  马上回来
okay.
好的
Okay.
没问题
Not to pry, but when you said
不是我八卦  但当你提到
carlos took you to st.barth
卡洛斯带你去圣巴斯
Oh, yeah, we lived together for a while back in the day.
正是  以前我们同居过一段时间
Oh! gaby didn't mention that.
加布没提过这事
See, that is what i love about her.
所以我才挺喜欢她的
Most women would freak out
大多数女人看到老公
If their husband hired an ex-girlfriend
雇佣前女友  都会抓狂
And they were working together unchaperoned.
况且他们还在时常单独处事
But she's got the confidence to just be cool with it.
她对我们相当有信心  态度很冷静
Yeah. yeah, that gaby's a real class act.
是啊  正是  的确是最典型的加布
Jessie, i-i am so sorry.
杰西  我真的很抱歉
Why? you were just being honest.
为什么  你实话实说而已
Still, uh...
还是那句话
I never meant to lead you on.
我不是有意要误导你
Uh-huh. well, i was planning on giving you
不管怎样  我本来就打算
A good evaluation anyway,
给你一个好评
So... everything's fine.
万事大吉
Look, i need this job.
我很想要这份工作
But even if i didn't,
但要是未能如愿
I would still like you as a person.
我还是像正常人一样看待你
Please, stop. i don't need your pity.
别来这套了  我不需要你同情
You know, i don't get why people say that.
我搞不懂怎么大家都爱这么说
I-i love pity.
我就喜欢同情
Pity means someone is trying to understand
同情  意味着有人正试图理解
What you're going through,
你究竟经历了什么
That they sympathize, and i do.
并产生怜悯之心  我就是这样的人
Susan...
苏珊
I'm someone who never went out and looked for love.
我从不主动寻找真爱
I assumed it would find me. but it didn't.
我以为真爱会找到我  但没有
And now i'm making a fool of myself...
现在我却愚蠢地在一个
Throwing myself at straight women,
对一个异性恋女性投怀送抱
Because i'm so afraid of being alone.
是因为我害怕孤独
Now how can you possibly understand that?
你如何来理解这些
Well, here's how. um, i...
我是这么理解的
I've spent my whole life putting myself out there,
我的一生都在主动出击  寻找真爱
And, um, i'm still...
而我现在
Today, alone.
依然孤独一人
Just like you.
像你一样
It's not the same.
情况不一样
Well, okay, it's not,
好吧  是不一样
Because i'm alone but i'm not lonely 'cause i have friends.
我虽然独身但并不孤独  因为我有朋友
Love doesn't happen for everyone.
爱神不会眷顾每个人
I don't even know if it's gonna happen for me anymore.
我甚至不知道我还会否得到爱
But my friends are there for me no matter what,
但无论如何  我有很多朋友
And that helps.
她们支持我
So at the very least,
至少
You know, let me be there for you...
让我成为你的后盾
As a friend.
作为挚友
That'd be nice.
这样感觉不错
Do your friends hug?
你的朋友们会拥抱吗
What's that in the garbage can?
垃圾筒里是什么
My boots.
我的靴子
What are you doing here?
你在这里干嘛
I just wanted to see how your first day went.
我正准备听你说说  你伟大的首日
Sit. take a load off. spill it.
放下工作  好好倾诉一番
Oh, that is so thoughtful of you.
你真是太贴心了
-You're such a good friend.
-真是个好朋友
oh, well, you know me.
你了解我的
Yeah, i do.
我当然
So did you get a good office? were the people nice?
办公室如何  同事还好吗
Oh, what about lucy? do you like her?
露西怎样  你喜欢她吗
Actually... i am kinda tired.
其实  我今天挺累了
I think i'm going to head inside.
我还是先回去了
Ooh! what's going on?
怎么了啊
I mentioned lucy, and you get all weird.
我提到了露西  你突然怪怪的
Is something going on with her... and carlos?
是不是有事发生啊  她和卡洛斯
What? no.
什么  没有
I'm sure she's just affectionate.
我只肯定  她很可爱的
whoa. what do you mean by affectionate?
什么  什么叫很可爱
Well, it's probably nothing.
其实也没什么
But when carlos works on his computer at home,
但是  当卡洛斯在家用电脑时
Does he take his shirt off there, too?
会把衣服脱下来吗
That son of a-- i'm gonna kill him!
这狗娘...  我要杀了他
No, you won't get the chance
不  你想也别想
'cause i'm gonnai'm gonna kill h
我先杀了你
The houselights are up, gaby. you can drop the act.
华灯初放  加布  你不用再掩饰了
You only helped me get this job because you needed a spy.
你帮我得到那份工作  只是要我做特工而已
How dare you!
你竟敢这么说
And, yes, i did!
是的  就是这么回事
Gaby!
加布
You needed a job. i did you a favor.
你在找工作  我帮个小忙
And then i brought you hot cocoa.
然后我给你买了杯热可可
-Why don't you ever thank me?
-你总得谢谢我吧
because you used me!
因为你利用了我
At least when i asked you for a favor, i was up front
至少我请你帮忙时  我是直截了当
were you miss "they offered me $100,000 a year"?
你怎么不想想"他们给我年薪10万"
Oh, you found out about that?
你发现了
Honey, i've played poker with you for the past nine years.
亲爱的  过去的9年里我一直和你玩扑克
I think i can tell when you're bluffing.
你要是撒谎  我一看就看出来了
Okay, it's true. i used you to get more money,
那好  事实如此  我为了提高薪水利用了你
-But you used me first.
-但你先利用了我
fine. we're a couple of users.
那好  我们是一对奸人
The big question is, are we still friends?
大前提是  我们还是朋友吗
Do i still get my salary?
薪水还是那么多吗
Will you still be my spy?
你肯继续当特工吗
Dave, i'm curious about something.
大卫  有些事我很好奇
What about?
什么事
Well, how do you feel about kids?
对于孩子  你感觉如何
Kids?
小孩
Yeah. haven't you ever wanted one?
有没有过小孩
Is this your coy way of telling me you want a child?
你是用含蓄地方式表达  你想要个孩子吗
Maybe. i hardly get to see travers anymore
我好久没有见查维斯了
Now that he's off at prep school.
他现在已从预科学校毕业了
And i always wanted a girl.
我一直想要个女儿
Doesn't that sound like heaven?
要是一个有着金色卷发的女孩
A beautiful little girl
降临到世上
With blonde curls.
是否是天堂的恩赐
I had this... friend
我有个朋友
Who had a little girl.
有个女儿
From the moment she was born,
从她出生那一刻起
She was his whole life.
她成了他生命的全部
Unfortunately, she was in an accident..
不幸的是  她在一次意外中
And died.
死亡了
He told me that when that happened,
他告诉我那一刻
A part of him died, too.
他生命的一部分也逝去了
He spent the rest of his life
他的余生
In a kind of... daze,
一直在茫然中度过
he's always...
他一直在想
Wondering exactly how old she would've been,
此时的女儿  应该多大了
What she would've looked like.
长得还漂亮吗
No.
不
I don't think i'd want a child.
我不要孩子
It's just not worth it.
这不值
You okay, babe?
宝贝  你还好吗
I'm just sad for your friend.
只是为你的朋友伤心
I had hoped that this compulsion to steal
我一度希望关于偷窃强迫症的问题
Was something we could solve privately,
能够私底下解决掉
But orson seems unable--
但奥森看起来不愿意
Or unwilling--
没这个能力
To control himself.
来控制好自己
Is that true, orson? are you unable to control yourself?
是真的吗  奥森  你是否无法控制住自己
You'll see when he leaves, and your lamp is missing.
等他走的时候  你一定会发现你台灯不见了
So... how do you want to proceed?
那么  你准备如何进行治疗
Would you like to begin with some couples counseling?
需要从心理咨询开始吗
This isn't my problem, dr. bernstein.
这不是我的问题  伯恩斯坦医生
He's the sick one.
有病的是他
Fix him.
把他治好
You know why she's so angry?
你知道她为什么这么生气
Because this is something she can'tcontrol,
因为这件事她无法控制
And i love it.
而我就爱顶着干
Now there's no phone in the cabin,
野外木屋里没有装电话
But if it's an emergency, you can reach me on my cell.
但如果有要紧事  打我手机就行了
You just be careful out there.
出门在外  小心为好
I don't know what i'd do without you.
没有你  我都不知如何是好
Bye.
再见
Here's the article that lady was looking for.
那位女士在寻找的文章在这儿
You want me to fax it?
要我传真过去吗
Ah, take your time. she's a pain in the ass.
这不急  她不好惹
She's pretty hot, though.
但她很性感
How does that help me?
对我有什么用
She can wait until tomorrow.
她能等到明天
You can find them almost anywhere--
这事处处可见
Friendly people with hidden agendas--
朋友之间  暗藏着协议
The woman who uses her neighbor
一个女人  利用她的邻居
To get herself a job...
为自己重入职场
The wife who uses her influence
太太使用她的影响力
To hire a friendly spy...
雇佣了一名贴心的特工
The husband who uses his charm
丈夫利用自己的魅力
To steal from his friends...
从朋友那里行窃
And you can be sure the friendliest people of all
可以肯定的是  表面风平浪静的好友
Have agendas that won't ever be discovered...
其实暗藏着波涛汹涌
Not until...
到发现时
It's too late.
为时已晚